Merrimack Films records 7064
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series III. Audiovisual Materials, 1973-2007
  - III.b. Betacam/Betamax
    - Troubled Partnerships, 1999; Betacam SP (Box 14, Item 2)
      Duplication Master. No.15757.
    - Troubled Partnerships: When Labor and Management Can't Make It Work, 1999; Betacam SP (Box 14, Item 3)
      PAL. No.15767
    - Partners: Bethlehem Steel and the United Steelworkers, 1996; Betacam SP (Box 14, Item 4)
    - Partners: Bethlehem Steel and the United Steelworkers, 1996; Betacam SP (Box 14, Item 5)
      No.22328.
    - Partners: Bethlehem Steel and the United Steelworkers, 1996; Betacam SP (Box 14, Item 6)
      PAL. No.26968.
    - Struggling Unions, 2002; Betacam SP (Box 14, Item 7)
      Duplication Master. No.21900.
    - Struggling Unions, 2002; Betacam SP (Box 14, Item 8)
      PAL. No.21945.
    - Working Together: Saturn and the UAW, 1994; Betacam SP (Box 14, Item 9)
    - Working Together: Saturn and the UAW, 1994; Betacam SP (Box 14, Item 10)
    - Rustbelt Phoenix: Saving the American Steel Industry, 2006; Betacam SP (Box 14, Item 11)
      Duplication Master. Minus Closed Caption.
    - Rustbelt Phoenix: Saving the American Steel Industry, 2006; Betacam SP (Box 14, Item 12)
      Closed Captioned.
    - Remaking Cities, Undated; Betacam SP (Box 14, Item 13)
      Dub for Merrimack Films.
    - Sparrows Point Division, Undated; Betacam SP (Box 14, Item 14)
      Basic oxygen furnace; continuous caster; 80" hot strip mill; hot dip galvanize line; Aerials; hot metal submarine car; L-blast furnace
    - Struggling Unions: Atlanta, 1999-05-07; Betacam SP (Box 15, Item 1)
    - Struggling Unions: Atlanta, 1999-05-07; Betacam SP (Box 15, Item 2)
    - Struggling Unions: Atlanta, 1999-05-07; Betacam SP (Box 15, Item 3)
    - Struggling Unions: Atlanta, 1999-05-07; Betacam SP (Box 15, Item 4)
    - Struggling Unions: Atlanta, 1999-05-07; Betacam SP (Box 15, Item 5)
    - Struggling Unions: Atlanta, 1999-05-07; Betacam SP (Box 15, Item 6)
      Tape #6
    - Struggling Unions: Atlanta, 1999-05-07; Betacam SP (Box 15, Item 7)
      Tape #7
    - Struggling Unions: Atlanta, 1999-05-07; Betacam SP (Box 15, Item 8)
      Tape #8
    - Struggling Unions: Atlanta, 1999-05-07; Betacam SP (Box 15, Item 9)
      Tape #9
    - Struggling Unions: Atlanta, 1999-05-07; Betacam SP (Box 15, Item 10)
      Tape #10
    - Struggling Unions: Atlanta, 1999-05-07; Betacam SP (Box 15, Item 11)
      Tape #11
    - Struggling Unions: Atlanta, 1999-05-08; Betacam SP (Box 15, Item 12)
      Tape #12
    - Struggling Unions: Atlanta, 1999-05-08; Betacam SP (Box 15, Item 13)
      Tape #13
    - Struggling Unions: Atlanta, 1999-05-08; Betacam SP (Box 15, Item 14)
      Tape #14
    - Struggling Unions: Atlanta, 1999-05-08; Betacam SP (Box 15, Item 15)
      Tape #15
    - Struggling Unions: Atlanta, 1999-05-08; Betacam SP (Box 15, Item 16)
      Tape #16
    - Struggling Unions: Atlanta, 1999-05-08; Betacam SP (Box 15, Item 17)
      Tape #17
    - Struggling Unions: Atlanta, 1999-05-08; Betacam SP (Box 15, Item 18)
      Tape #18
    - Struggling Unions: Atlanta, 1999-05-08; Betacam SP (Box 15, Item 19)
      Tape #19
    - Struggling Unions: Atlanta, 1999-05-08; Betacam SP (Box 15, Item 20)
      Tape #20
    - Struggling Unions: Atlanta, 1999-05-08; Betacam SP (Box 15, Item 21)
      Tape #22
    - Struggling Unions: Atlanta, 1999-05-08; Betacam SP (Box 15, Item 22)
      Tape #23
    - Struggling Unions: Boston, 1999-07-01; Betacam SP (Box 15, Item 23)
    - Struggling Unions: Boston, 1999-07-01; Betacam SP (Box 15, Item 24)
      Tape #2. B-Roll, Big Dig, Drive-Bys, Assembling for rally as Government Center, stand-up interviews with union members.
    - Struggling Unions: Boston, 1999-07-01; Betacam SP (Box 15, Item 25)
      Tape #3. Union march from Government Center to State House, speeches.
    - Struggling Unions: Boston, 1999-07-01; Betacam SP (Box 15, Item 26)
      Tape #4. Union rally speeches, wide shots at end.
    - Struggling Unions: Boston, 1999-07-01; Betacam SP (Box 15, Item 27)
      Tape #5. Interview with Jim McDermott.
    - Struggling Unions: Cambridge, 1999-08-02; Betacam SP (Box 15, Item 28)
    - Struggling Unions: Cambridge, 1999-08-02; Betacam SP (Box 15, Item 29)
    - Struggling Unions: Cambridge, 1999-08-02; Betacam SP (Box 15, Item 30)
    - Struggling Unions: Cambridge, 1999-08-02; Betacam SP (Box 15, Item 31)
    - Struggling Unions: New Jersey, 2000-04-21; Betacam SP (Box 16, Item 7)
      Tape #1. Edwin Stier Interview.
    - Struggling Unions: New Jersey, 2000-04-21; Betacam SP (Box 16, Item 8)
      Tape #2. Edwin Stier Interview.
    - Struggling Unions: New Jersey, 2000-04-21; Betacam SP (Box 16, Item 9)
      Tape #3. Edwin Stier Interview.
    - Struggling Unions: New Jersey, 2000-04-21; Betacam SP (Box 16, Item 10)
      Tape #4. Edwin Stier Interview. B-Roll.
    - Struggling Unions: New York City, 1999-09-22; Betacam SP (Box 16, Item 11)
    - Struggling Unions: New York City, 1999-09; Betacam SP (Box 16, Item 12)
    - Struggling Unions: New York City, 1999-09; Betacam SP (Box 16, Item 13)
    - Struggling Unions: New York City, 1999-09; Betacam SP (Box 16, Item 14)
    - Struggling Unions: New York City, 1999-09; Betacam SP (Box 16, Item 15)
    - Struggling Unions: New York City, 1999-09-29; Betacam SP (Box 16, Item 16)
    - Struggling Unions: New York City, 1999-09; Betacam SP (Box 16, Item 17)
    - Struggling Unions: New York City, 1999-09; Betacam SP (Box 16, Item 18)
    - Struggling Unions: New York City, 1999-09; Betacam SP (Box 16, Item 19)
    - Struggling Unions: New York City, 1999-09; Betacam SP (Box 16, Item 20)
    - Struggling Unions: New York City, 1999-09; Betacam SP (Box 16, Item 21)
    - Struggling Unions: New York City, 1999-09; Betacam SP (Box 16, Item 22)
    - Struggling Unions: New York City, 1999-09; Betacam SP (Box 16, Item 23)
    - Struggling Unions: New York City, 1999-09; Betacam SP (Box 16, Item 24)
    - Struggling Unions: Detroit, 1999-04-24; Betacam SP (Box 16, Item 25)
    - Struggling Unions: Detroit, 1999-04-24; Betacam SP (Box 16, Item 26)
    - Struggling Unions: John Lisanti Interview, 2001-12-03; Betacam SP (Box 16, Item 27)
    - Struggling Unions: John Lisanti Interview, 2001-12-03; Betacam SP (Box 16, Item 28)
    - Struggling Unions: John Lisanti Interview, 2001-12-03; Betacam SP (Box 16, Item 29)
    - Spring Hill, 2006-08-12; Betacam SP (Box 17, Item 1)
    - Spring Hill, 2006-08-12; Betacam SP (Box 17, Item 2)
      Tape #2. Group discussion, AM.
    - Spring Hill, 2006-08-12; Betacam SP (Box 17, Item 3)
    - Spring Hill, 2006-08-12; Betacam SP (Box 17, Item 4)
    - Spring Hill, 2006-08-12; Betacam SP (Box 17, Item 5)
      Tape #5. Start of four rank and filer interviews.
    - Spring Hill, 2006-08-12; Betacam SP (Box 17, Item 6)
      Tape #6. Four rank and filer interviews continued.
    - Spring Hill, 2006-08-12; Betacam SP (Box 17, Item 7)
      Tape #7. End of four rank and filer interviews.
    - Spring Hill, 2006-08-12; Betacam SP (Box 17, Item 8)
    - Spring Hill, 2006-08-12; Betacam SP (Box 17, Item 9)
    - Spring Hill, 2006-08-12; Betacam SP (Box 17, Item 10)
      Tape #10. B-Roll.
    - Spring Hill, 2007-03-22; Betacam SP (Box 17, Item 11)
    - Spring Hill, 2007-03-22; Betacam SP (Box 17, Item 12)
    - Spring Hill, 2007-03-22; Betacam SP (Box 17, Item 13)
    - Spring Hill, 2007-03-22; Betacam SP (Box 17, Item 14)
    - Spring Hill, 2007-03-22; Betacam SP (Box 17, Item 15)
    - Spring Hill, 2007-03-22; Betacam SP (Box 17, Item 16)
    - Spring Hill, 2007-03-22; Betacam SP (Box 17, Item 17)
    - Spring Hill, 2007-03-22; Betacam SP (Box 17, Item 18)
      Tape #8. B-Roll in Mike Herron's office.
    - Saturn 2: Detroit, 2007-06-26; Betacam SP (Box 17, Item 19)
    - Saturn 2: Detroit, 2007-06-26; Betacam SP (Box 17, Item 20)
      Tape #2. B-Roll.
    - Saturn 2: Detroit, 2007-06-26; Betacam SP (Box 17, Item 21)
    - Saturn 2: Detroit, 2007-06-26; Betacam SP (Box 17, Item 22)
    - Saturn 2: Detroit, 2007-06-26; Betacam SP (Box 17, Item 23)
    - Saturn 2: Detroit, 2007-06-26; Betacam SP (Box 17, Item 24)
    - Saturn, 1993-08-26; Betacam SP (Box 17, Item 25)
    - Saturn, 1993-08-26; Betacam SP (Box 17, Item 26)
      Tape #2. Start of meeting.
    - Saturn, 1993-08-26; Betacam SP (Box 17, Item 27)
      Tape #3. Meeting continued.
    - Saturn, 1993-08-26; Betacam SP (Box 17, Item 28)
      Tape #4. Subs team, feeding assembly line.
    - Saturn, 1993-08-26; Betacam SP (Box 17, Item 29)
    - Saturn, 1993-08-26; Betacam SP (Box 17, Item 30)
      Tape #6. Assembly line.
    - Saturn, 1993-08-26; Betacam SP (Box 17, Item 31)
    - Working Together: Saturn and the UAW, 1993-12-13; Betacam SP (Box 18, Item 1)
    - Working Together: Saturn and the UAW, 1993-12-13; Betacam SP (Box 18, Item 2)
    - Working Together: Saturn and the UAW, 1993-12-13; Betacam SP (Box 18, Item 3)
    - Working Together: Saturn and the UAW, 1993-12-13; Betacam SP (Box 18, Item 4)
    - Working Together: Saturn and the UAW, 1993-12-13; Betacam SP (Box 18, Item 5)
    - Working Together: Saturn and the UAW, 1993-12-13; Betacam SP (Box 18, Item 6)
    - Saturn, 1994-04-05; Betacam SP (Box 18, Item 7)
    - Working Together Stills, 1994-04-04; Betacam SP (Box 18, Item 8)
      Tape #2 of 2. Includes Toyota.
    - Unions in Crisis Boston Shoot, 1992-06-24; Betacam SP (Box 19, Item 1)
      Reel #1
    - Unions in Crisis Boston Shoot, 1992-06-24; Betacam SP (Box 19, Item 2)
      Reel #2
    - Unions in Crisis Boston Shoot, 1992-06-24; Betacam SP (Box 19, Item 3)
      Reel #3
    - Unions in Crisis First Frame Work Print, Undated; Betacam SP (Box 19, Item 4)
    - Unions in Crisis First Frame Work Print, Undated; Betacam SP (Box 19, Item 5)
    - Unions in Crisis First Frame Work Print, Undated; Betacam SP (Box 19, Item 6)
    - Sparrows Point, 1995-11-30; Betacam SP (Box 19, Item 9)
    - Sparrows Point, 1995-11-30; Betacam SP (Box 19, Item 10)
    - Sparrows Point, 1995-11-30; Betacam SP (Box 19, Item 11)
    - Sparrows Point, 1995-12-01; Betacam SP (Box 19, Item 12)
    - Sparrows Point, 1995-12-01; Betacam SP (Box 19, Item 13)
    - Sparrows Point, Tin Mill Meeting, 2005-05-19; Betacam SP (Box 19, Item 14)
    - Sparrows Point, Undated; Betacam SP (Box 19, Item 15)
    - Sparrows Point, Tin Mill Meeting, Undated; Betacam SP (Box 19, Item 16)
    - Sparrows Point, Tin Mill Meeting, Undated; Betacam SP (Box 19, Item 17)
    - Sparrows Point, Tin Mill Meeting, Undated; Betacam SP (Box 19, Item 18)
    - Sparrows Point, Undated; Betacam SP (Box 19, Item 19)
    - Sparrows Point, Undated; Betacam SP (Box 19, Item 20)
    - Sparrows Point, Undated; Betacam SP (Box 19, Item 21)
    - Sparrows Point, 2001-08; Betacam SP (Box 20, Item 1)
      B-Roll.
    - Troubled Partnerships, 1997-03-20; Betacam SP (Box 20, Item 3)
    - Troubled Partnerships, 1997-03-20; Betacam SP (Box 20, Item 4)
    - Troubled Partnerships, 1997-03-20; Betacam SP (Box 20, Item 5)
    - Troubled Partnerships, 1997-03-20; Betacam SP (Box 20, Item 6)
    - Troubled Partnerships, 1997-03-20; Betacam SP (Box 20, Item 7)
    - Troubled Partnerships, 1997-03-20; Betacam SP (Box 20, Item 8)
    - Troubled Partnerships, 1997-03-20; Betacam SP (Box 20, Item 9)
    - Troubled Partnerships, 1997-03-20; Betacam SP (Box 20, Item 10)
    - Troubled Partnerships, 1997-03-20; Betacam SP (Box 20, Item 11)
    - Troubled Partnerships, 1997-03-20; Betacam SP (Box 20, Item 12)
    - Troubled, 1997-09-17; Betacam SP (Box 20, Item 14)
      Tape 20.
    - Troubled, 1997-09-17; Betacam SP (Box 20, Item 15)
      Tape 21.
    - Troubled, 1997-09-17; Betacam SP (Box 20, Item 16)
      Tape 23.
    - Stills, Partners, Undated; Betacam SP (Box 20, Item 17)
      Tape 26.
    - Partnership, Sparrows Point, Safety Meeting, 1996-02-16; Betacam SP (Box 21, Item 1)
      Tape #12.
    - Partnership, Sparrows Point, 2, 1996-02-16; Betacam SP (Box 21, Item 2)
      Tape #13.
    - National Archives Footage, 1996-02-29; Betacam SP (Box 21, Item 3)
    - National Archives Footage, 1996-02-29; Betacam SP (Box 21, Item 4)
      Tape #2.
    - Pittsburgh, American Locker, 1996-03-15; Betacam SP (Box 21, Item 5)
      Tape #2. 016.
    - Pittsburgh, Monsignor Rice, 1996-03-15; Betacam SP (Box 21, Item 6)
      Tape #3. 017.
    - Pittsburgh, Steelworkers, 1996-03-15; Betacam SP (Box 21, Item 7)
      Tape #4. 018.
    - Pittsburgh, United Steelworkers, 1996-03-15; Betacam SP (Box 21, Item 8)
      Tape #5. 019.
    - San Diego, IRRA Panel and Interviews, 2004-01-04; Betacam SP (Box 21, Item 20)
      Tape #11. Conclusion of Panel #2 and B-Roll.
    - Akron Ohio Tape #1, 1997-07-28; Betacam SP (Box 21, Item 21)
      Tape #11.
    - Akron Ohio Tape #2, 1997-07-28; Betacam SP (Box 21, Item 22)
      Tape #12. Cutaways, outside of Union Hall, Goodyear plant.
    - Merrimack Films, 1998-12-17; Betacam SP (Box 21, Item 23)
      Tape #13. John on camera.
    - Merrimack Films, 1998-12-17; Betacam SP (Box 21, Item 24)
      Tape #14. John on camera, move stills.
    - USWA Camp Justice, 1996-10-02; Betacam SP (Box 21, Item 25)
    - USWA Running Over the American Dream, Undated; Betacam SP (Box 21, Item 26)
    - USWA Rally and March to B/F Headquarters, 1996-07-12; Betacam SP (Box 21, Item 27)
      Tape #3.
    - Press Conference of BSF Union Workers in Japan, 1996-07-12; Betacam SP (Box 21, Item 28)
    - Picket Line Shots, Undated; Betacam SP (Box 21, Item 29)
    - Polaroid. Production Line Assembly Captiva and Spectra, Undated; Betacam SP (Box 21, Item 30)
      B-Roll (MOS).
    - Nashville Shoot Tape 2, Undated; Betacam SP (Box 21, Item 31)
      Tape #42.
    - Nashville Shoot Bridgestone Plant, Undated; Betacam SP (Box 21, Item 32)
      Tape #46. B-Roll.
    - Inside Penwood Power Plant, 1996-02-16; Betacam SP (Box 21, Item 33)
      Tape #14.
    - ABC New Video Source, 2001-12-11; Betacam SP (Box 23, Item 4)
      Tracking #16694; Order #25438.
    - ABC New Video Source, 1998-11-10; Betacam SP (Box 24, Item 16)
      Tracking #9455; Order #11972.
    - 1989 Eastern Strike also Misc. Labor Stock, Betamax (Box 1, Item 1)
      There are various videos on this cassette
    - Eastern Teamsters June 91 Connection, 1992-06; Betamax (Box 1, Item 2)
    - Eastern Strike 1989, Betamax (Box 1, Item 3)
    - 620 to 650 Pittston vs UAW Strike union busting, Undated; Betamax (Box 1, Item 4)
    - Giveback Update, Undated; Betamax (Box 1, Item 5)
    - 620 to 650 Pittston vs UAW Strike union busting, 1987; Betamax (Box 1, Item 6)
    - Misc. Labor;GM Layoffs;Cat Strike, Undated; Betamax (Box 1, Item 7)
    - Nissan UAW election, Undated; Betamax (Box 1, Item 8)
    - Int. Tom Keegel Tape 1 B-Roll, 2000-05-10; Betamax (Box 1, Item 9)
    - Int. Tom Keegel Tape 2 B-Roll, 2000-05-11; Betamax (Box 1, Item 10)
    - Int. John Murphy Tape 3 B-Roll, 2000-05-12; Betamax (Box 1, Item 11)
    - Int. John Murphy/ Pat Szymanski Tape 4 B-Roll, 2000-05-13; Betamax (Box 1, Item 12)
    - Int. Pat Szymanski Tape 5 B-Roll, 2000-05-14; Betamax (Box 1, Item 13)
    - Struggling Unions Labor Notes Conference- Detroit, 1999-04-24; Betamax (Box 1, Item 14)
    - Struggling Unions Labor Notes Conference- Detroit, 1999-04-24; Betamax (Box 1, Item 15)
    - Struggling Unions Labor Notes Conference- Detroit, 1999-04-24; Betamax (Box 1, Item 16)
    - Struggling Unions Labor Notes Conference- Detroit, 1999-04-24; Betamax (Box 1, Item 17)
    - Struggling Unions Labor Notes Conference- Detroit, 1999-04-24; Betamax (Box 1, Item 18)
    - Struggling Unions Labor Notes Conference- Detroit, 1999-04-24; Betamax (Box 1, Item 19)
    - Struggling Unions Labor Notes Conference- Detroit, 1999-04-24; Betamax (Box 1, Item 20)
      Tape 9
    - Struggling Unions Labor Notes Conference- Detroit, 1999-04-24; Betamax (Box 1, Item 21)
    - Struggling Unions Labor Notes Conference- Detroit, 1999-04-24; Betamax (Box 1, Item 22)
  - III.c. DV/MiniDV
    - LTV News Footage, 2005-11-07; DVCAM (Box 11, Item 31)
      Tape 1. Transfer from VHS.
    - LTV News Footage, 2005-11-07; DVCAM (Box 11, Item 32)
      Tape 2. Transfer from VHS.
    - Unions in Crisis, 1992; DVCAM (Box 12, Item 25)
    - Union Democracy, Undated; DVCAM (Box 12, Item 26)
    - What Happened to Saturn, 2007-12-18; DVCAM (Box 12, Item 27)
    - Saturn, 2007-12-01; DVCAM (Box 17, Item 32)
      Tape #1. Ben on camera.
    - Saturn, 2007-12-01; DVCAM (Box 17, Item 33)
      Tape #2. Ben on camera.
    - Sloan School, MIT, 2001-07-31; DVCAM (Box 23, Item 7)
      Tape #1. Book B-Roll.
    - Sloan School, MIT, 2001-07-31; DVCAM (Box 23, Item 8)
    - Sloan School, MIT, 2001-07-31; DVCAM (Box 23, Item 9)
      Tape #3. B-Roll of Tom.
    - Struggling Unions, Undated; DVCAM mini (Box 23, Item 10)
      Transfer VHS to DVCAM.
    - Struggling Unions: Stills, 2001-12; DVCAM mini (Box 23, Item 11)
      PD100A.
    - Carey Stills, Undated; DVCAM mini (Box 23, Item 12)
    - Camp Steel, 2005-11; miniDV (Box 11, Item 33)
    - Last Saturn VUE Built, 2007-03-30; miniDV (Box 23, Item 13)
      GM Spring Hill. B-Roll.
    - Saturn ION and Saturn VUE Manufacturing, 2007; miniDV (Box 23, Item 14)
      GM Spring Hill. Media B-Roll and Product B-Roll.
    - Hybrid VUE, 2007; miniDV (Box 23, Item 15)
    - ION and VUE Production, 2007; miniDV (Box 23, Item 16)
      GM Spring Hill. Media B-Roll.
  - III.d. U-matic
    - Crisis Bargaining, Undated; Umatic (Box 5, Item 1)
    - Givebacks: The UAW and the Auto Industry, 1986; Umatic (Box 5, Item 2)
    - Loose Bolts?, Undated; Umatic (Box 5, Item 3)
      VCTM 50-#3B. Dub
    - Loose Bolts?, Undated; Umatic (Box 5, Item 4)
      VCTM 32-#4. Red Ball Films.
    - Union Democracy, 1986; Umatic (Box 5, Item 7)
      VCTM 147-#008
    - Union Democracy, 1986; Umatic (Box 5, Item 8)
      VCTM 147-#01
    - Union Democracy, 1986; Umatic (Box 5, Item 9)
      VCTM 147-#019
    - Unions in Crisis, 1992-11-04; Umatic (Box 5, Item 10)
    - Unions in Crisis, 1992-11-04; Umatic (Box 5, Item 11)
    - Unions in Crisis, 1992-11-04; Umatic (Box 5, Item 12)
    - Working Together: Saturn and the UAW, 1994; Umatic (Box 5, Item 13)
    - Working Together: Saturn and the UAW, 1994; Umatic (Box 5, Item 14)
    - Givebacks: Audio Master #2, Undated; Umatic (Box 7, Item 9)
    - Ford Collection #1, Undated; Umatic (Box 7, Item 22)
      8 videos
    - Union Democracy, Undated; Umatic (Box 7, Item 23)
      April. 6 videos.
    - Cannon Mills Tape #1, Undated; Umatic (Box 7, Item 24)
      Interview of union official, shots of main office.
    - Cannon Mills Tape #2, Undated; Umatic (Box 7, Item 25)
      Workers enter and leave during shift change
    - Cannon Mills Tape #3, Undated; Umatic (Box 7, Item 26)
      Interviews at Holiday Inn
    - Cannon Mills Tape #4, Undated; Umatic (Box 7, Item 27)
      Election results
    - Union Democracy Tape #1, Undated; Umatic (Box 8, Item 1)
    - Union Democracy Tape #3, Undated; Umatic (Box 8, Item 2)
    - Union Democracy Tape #4, Undated; Umatic (Box 8, Item 3)
    - Union Democracy Tape #5, Undated; Umatic (Box 8, Item 4)
    - Union Democracy Tape #6, Undated; Umatic (Box 8, Item 5)
    - Union Democracy Tape #7, Undated; Umatic (Box 8, Item 6)
    - Union Democracy Tape #8, Undated; Umatic (Box 8, Item 7)
    - Union Democracy Tape #9, Undated; Umatic (Box 8, Item 8)
    - Union Democracy Tape #10, Undated; Umatic (Box 8, Item 9)
    - Union Democracy Tape #11, Undated; Umatic (Box 8, Item 10)
    - Union Democracy Tape #12, Undated; Umatic (Box 8, Item 11)
    - Givebacks Tape #2, Undated; Umatic (Box 8, Item 12)
    - Givebacks Tape #4, Undated; Umatic (Box 8, Item 13)
      Audio track.
    - Givebacks: The UAW and the Auto Industry, 1986; Umatic (Box 8, Item 14)
    - Loose Bolts?, Undated; Umatic (Box 8, Item 15)
      VCTM 32-#123
    - Loose Bolts?, Undated; Umatic (Box 8, Item 16)
      VCTM 32-#126
    - Taxes, Taxes, Undated; Umatic (Box 8, Item 17)
    - Merrimack Washington #1, Undated; Umatic (Box 9, Item 11)
      RF-21
    - Merrimack Washington #2, Undated; Umatic (Box 9, Item 12)
      RF-22
    - Merrimack Washington #3, Undated; Umatic (Box 9, Item 13)
      RF-23
    - Merrimack Washington #4, Undated; Umatic (Box 9, Item 14)
      RF-24
    - Merrimack Washington #5, Undated; Umatic (Box 9, Item 15)
      RF-25
    - Merrimack Washington #6, Undated; Umatic (Box 9, Item 16)
      RF-26
    - Labor Relations Board #1, 1986-10-16; Umatic (Box 9, Item 17)
      RF-509
    - Labor Relations Board #2, 1986-10-16; Umatic (Box 9, Item 18)
      RF-510
    - Labor Relations Board #3, 1986-10-16; Umatic (Box 9, Item 19)
      RF-511
    - Labor Relations Board #4, 1986-10-16; Umatic (Box 9, Item 20)
      RF-512
    - Labor Relations Board #5, 1986-10-16; Umatic (Box 9, Item 21)
      RF-513
    - Labor Relations Board #1, 1986-10-16; Umatic (Box 9, Item 22)
      RF-509. With time code.
    - Tape #1: Car, Ambiance Sound, Les Talking, Undated; Umatic (Box 10, Item 11)
    - Tape #3: Narration #3 and 6, Undated; Umatic (Box 10, Item 12)
      Castaways, foreign cars.
    - Kansas City Reel 1, Undated; Umatic (Box 10, Item 13)
    - Kansas City Reel 2, Undated; Umatic (Box 10, Item 14)
    - Kansas City Reel 3, Undated; Umatic (Box 10, Item 15)
    - Kansas City Reel 4, Undated; Umatic (Box 10, Item 16)
    - Labor Relations Board #2, 1986-10-16; Umatic (Box 10, Item 17)
    - Union Democracy, 1986; Umatic (Box 10, Item 18)
      VCTM 147-#015
    - Union Democracy, 1986; Umatic (Box 10, Item 19)
    - Union Democracy, 1986; Umatic (Box 10, Item 20)
      No.15932
    - Crisis Bargaining, 1985-02; Umatic (Box 10, Item 21)
      VCTM 100-#125
    - Taxes, Taxes, 1979-10-11; Umatic (Box 10, Item 22)
      VCTM 20-#1
    - Ford Collection Tape #4, Undated; Umatic (Box 12, Item 24)
      2 videos.
    - Givebacks, Undated; Umatic (Box 13, Item 1)
      A 46-#3
    - Givebacks, Undated; Umatic (Box 13, Item 2)
      A 46-#4
    - Givebacks, 1983; Umatic (Box 13, Item 3)
    - Givebacks: The UAW and the Auto Industry, 1986; Umatic (Box 13, Item 4)
    - Givebacks: The UAW and the Auto Industry, 1986; Umatic (Box 13, Item 5)
    - Givebacks: The UAW and the Auto Industry, 1986; Umatic (Box 13, Item 6)
    - Loose Bolts?, Undated; Umatic (Box 13, Item 7)
      VCTM 32-#124
    - Loose Bolts?, Undated; Umatic (Box 13, Item 8)
      PAL. No.15931.
    - Crisis Bargaining, 1979; Umatic (Box 13, Item 9)
      PAL. No.15937.
    - Crisis Bargaining, 1984-12-28; Umatic (Box 13, Item 10)
      No.15945.
    - Crisis Bargaining, Undated; Umatic (Box 13, Item 11)
      VCTM 100-#14
    - Crisis Bargaining, Undated; Umatic (Box 13, Item 12)
      VCTM 100-#124
    - Working Together: Saturn and the UAW, 1994; Umatic (Box 13, Item 13)
    - Working Together: Saturn and the UAW, 1994; Umatic (Box 13, Item 14)
    - Working Together: Saturn and the UAW, 1994; Umatic (Box 13, Item 15)
    - Working Together: Saturn and the UAW, 1994; Umatic (Box 13, Item 16)
    - Ford Collection Tape #2, Undated; Umatic (Box 23, Item 25)
      7 videos.
    - Ford Collection Tape #3, Undated; Umatic (Box 23, Item 26)
      9 videos.
    - Givebacks: The UAW and the Auto Industry, 1983-07-15; Umatic (Box 24, Item 1)
      Dub.
    - Givebacks: The UAW and the Auto Industry, 1983-07-15; Umatic (Box 24, Item 2)
    - JFK Footage, Undated; Umatic (Box 24, Item 3)
    - Taxes, Taxes, Undated; Umatic (Box 24, Item 4)
      VCTM 65-#114
    - Taxes, Taxes, Undated; Umatic (Box 24, Item 5)
      VCTM 80-#113
    - Taxes, Taxes, 1979-10-11; Umatic (Box 24, Item 6)
      VCTM 65-#2
    - Union Democracy, 1986; Umatic (Box 24, Item 7)
      Sample
    - Union Democracy, 1986; Umatic (Box 24, Item 8)
      Back up.
    - Unions in Crisis: National Archives A, 1989-12; Umatic (Box 24, Item 9)